flyawaysimulation.com 2018-10-30

# Privacy Policy & Terms of Use - Fly Away Simulation

Below are the terms and conditions and the privacy policy for our website, Fly Away Simulation.

**Jump to:**

  * Terms and conditions of use
  * Privacy Policy

## Fly Away Simulation Terms and Conditions

Below are the terms and conditions for the use of our services.

### Payment

Payment for your 'Fly Away Simulation Lifetime Membership' is handled by Paypal Inc.  Cards accepted include Visa, Mastercard, Discover Novus, Amex, Switch, Solo and many other non-standard card types.  Security for your payment, and security of your payment details is Paypal Inc's responsibility, and their privacy statement and terms can be found on their website when making a purchase.

### Service Paid For

Upon signing up for a 'Fly Away Simulation Monthly Membership', you are paying for the use and bandwidth of the Fly Away server that is used to transit any resources such as images, text, files to your computer.  You are not paying for the download works of developers who created the files; they are freeware which are also available on many other internet resource sites.

### Service Agreed

As a  registered user of Fly Away Simulation, you are entitled to have access to your account for as long as the Fly Away Simulation site, [https://flyawaysimulation.com](https://flyawaysimulation.com/) is in business.  If anything should happen that Fly Away Simulation is no longer able to provide website features, or features provided for the sole purpose payment, no refunds will be offered and agreed. 

### Email Addresses and Communication from Us to You

By signing up, you agree that Fly Away Simulation may send newsletters, network messages and other e-mail based messages to the e-mail address you signed up with. You may unsubscribe from our newsletters at any time.

### External Linking Within the Forums

External links should only be posted within forum topics and messages if the final resource of the link cannot be obtained on or within the Fly Away Simulation network. External links mean links to websites that reside outside the Fly Away Simulation domain names. Resources may include download articles, other forum websites and news articles, but not restricted to these types. When posting a message with external links, you agree that your message may be edited and changed by administrators and moderators within our forums to update the link you posted to point to a local resource within the Fly Away Simulation Network. If you revert these edits and continue to revert these edits by the administrators, you will be warned once. If after the warning you continue to revert these edits, your account on Fly Away Simulation will be revoked. External linking within forum profile signatures is not permitted.

### Cancelation Policy for Monthly Membership

Any member may cancel their monthly membership at any time for any reason. Please note; we cannot cancel your membership for you or cancel it via an e-mail request. Users must login to their PayPal account and cancel their own membership via the PayPal website.

When you cancel a subscription via PayPal, you will still have full access to your account until the subscription term lapses. Access will be denied to the PRO features of the site under your account after the subscription term has lapsed if there is no active subscription on the account for the next months payment to be taken.

You may cancel your account at any time and for any reason and no notice needs to be given.

By making a payment to Fly Away Simulation, you agree to these terms and conditions and are fully aware that you agree to them by making a payment.

### Editorial Policy

Please note that a lot of our flight simulator and aviation news articles are submitted by developers and professionals within the aviation and flight simulation industry. We screen, edit and approve all articles manually before they are published. We maintain the utmost integrity on the articles and press releases we publish, however if you have comments on the content of any article published here, please feel free to use the [feedback](https://flyawaysimulation.com/contact/) form and provide us with your feedback. If you think that this article is copyrighted and does not belong on this site, and you are the copyright holder, please use the [feedback form](https://flyawaysimulation.com/contact/) to make us aware of this. Incorrectly published copyrighted works will be removed immediately upon request.

Top

* * *

## Privacy Policy

This specific Online Privacy Policy governs the manner that Fly Away Simulation gathers, utilizes, controls, as well as divulges data received via users (each, a "User") of <https://flyawaysimulation.com/> internet site ("Site"). This online privacy policy refers to the Site and all of the offerings, goods, and services available at Fly Away Simulation.

### Your own ID information and facts

We might acquire particular personal identity data from Users via many different approaches, which includes, however is not restricted to, when Users visit this website, sign in on the site, sign up for the e-newsletter, along with connection to other features, items, solutions, activities, information or resources we offer on our Site. Users could possibly be requested, as relevant, email address contact information or bank card data. Users might, nevertheless, visit our Site anonymously. We're going to gather individual personal identity data from Users only on condition that they willingly give this kind of data to us. Users can still refuse to provide individual identification data; with the exception that it may possibly stop these individuals from taking part in particular Site related functions.

### Non-personal identity data

We might gather non-personal identification details about a User if he or she connects with our Site. Non-personal ID details might include the internet browser brand name, the sort of personal computer and technological details about the User’s method of linking with our Site, for instance the operating system and also the Internet service providers employed as well as other corresponding material.

### Internet Browser Cookies

#### What Are Cookies?

Cookies are small files that are saved on your local device (computer, tablet, laptop etc.) by websites that you visit.  Cookies can be used for many different purposes which we describe in further detail below.

#### How We Use Cookies

We may use cookies to gather information from your visit to our site.  None of the data gathered will contain personal details or identifying data.  The data sought by the cookie helps us improve our website and any service offered to you.  Your web browser also has the option of blocking cookies entirely by changing your browser settings.  However, if you do block cookies, some areas of the website may not work as expected.

#### Types of Cookies We Use

##### Session Cookies

Session cookies allow us to ensure we display the correct pages and information from what you may select on the site giving you the best user experience.  For example, this could include redirecting you back to the correct page in order to create your account when signing up after payment.  Another example is when you log in to your account, it will ensure that the correct pages are displayed to reflect your logged-in status.

##### Persistent Cookies

Persistent cookies allow us to keep track of your preferred privacy settings.  They allow us to know whether you have accepted the website terms and conditions (specifically related to cookie options).  They can last up to 2 years or until you clear your web browser cookies or cache. 

##### Analytical Cookies

We use Google Analytics to monitor how many people visit the Site, what pages are popular and where visitors have arrived from.  We do not collect IP address information and all of the data gathered is anonymous.  Google Analytics has a special feature that we have enabled that anonymizes the IP address data before any storage or processing takes place.  We do not track pages with identifiable variables such as name, username or IP address contained in the URL.  Collecting this analytical data enables us to provide a better experience to our users.  No personally identifiable information is recorded in these cookies (applies globally) and when used they are always transmitted over SSL.

##### Advertising Cookies

We may display advertisements to you alongside content available on this Site.  We use the Google Adsense platform to display advertising on the Site.  

_Visitors inside the EEA:_

Any visitors to this Site from the EEA will not be displayed personalized advertisements and the Adsense platform will show only non-personalized ads to users in the EEA.

_For visitors outside the EEA:_

In order to display targeted advertisements, third-party vendors including Google will use browser cookies to generate relevant advertisements.  By using these cookies, the advertisements can be targeted more specifically to your browsing history.  Fly Away Simulation use the Google AdSense platform to deliver ads to our users and may also include third-party vendors and ad networks from within the Google AdSense platform.

You, the User may opt-out of personalized advertising from Google AdSense by visiting the following URL: <https://adssettings.google.com/>  You may also visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> to opt-out of third-party vendors' use of cookies for advertising purposes

### How we guard your data

We follow proper information collection, storage and handling methods and safety measures to shield against illegal access, modification, disclosure or destruction of your information and facts, login name, security password, transaction specifics and data saved on our Site.

Confidential and personal information exchange in-between the Site and its Users takes place across an SSL (Secure Socket Layer) guarded transmission channel and is encrypted and guarded with electronic digital signatures. Our Site is likewise in concurrence with PCI vulnerability benchmarks in order to make as secure a setting as is feasible for Users.

### Sharing your individual details

We don't distribute, deal, or rent out Users individual identification details to other people. We might distribute general aggregated group material not in connection with any private identification data relating to website visitors and users with our partners, reputable associates and marketers for the objectives defined previously.

### Third party internet sites

Users might find advertising, marketing, and other website content on our Site that connects to web sites and professional services of our associates, providers, promoters, sponsors, licensors as well as other organizations. We don't handle the information or hyperlinks that display on these internet sites and therefore are not accountable for the methods used by internet sites linked with or from the Site. Furthermore, these internet websites or companies, including their website content and URL links, could possibly be perpetually evolving and changing. These web sites and companies might have their own personal online privacy policies and client care guidelines. Browsing, connection or use of another online site, including website pages that may have a hyperlink to our Website, is subject to that web site's individual stipulations, rules, policies, and procedures.

### Modifications for this online privacy policy

Fly Away Simulation has the option to change this online privacy policy without notice. Whenever we do, we'll modify the current date at the end of this specific internet page. We strongly encourage Users to repeatedly check this document for any modifications to keep knowledgeable regarding how our company is helping to secure the private information and facts we gather. You understand and agree with the fact that it is your responsibility to examine this online privacy policy frequently and be attentive to adjustments and changes.

### Your validation of these stipulations

By employing this Site, you indicate your acknowledgement of this policy and terms of use. In the event you do not accept this policy, please do not utilize our Site. Your ongoing utilization of the Site after the publishing of adjustments to this policy shall be considered your endorsement and acceptance of these alterations.

## Contacting us

If you have any inquiries concerning this Privacy Policy, the procedures of this specific site, or your transactions with this site, please make sure to make contact with us by means of [our support ticketing system](https://flyawaysimulation.com/support/).

### Mailing Address

**Fly Away Simulation**  
c/o RBFTP Networks Ltd.  
Mountview Court  
1148 High Road  
Whetstone  
London  
N20 0RA  
United Kingdom

### Phone

**USA**  
+1-323-375-2119

**UK**  
+44-203-318-0477

Top

**This document was last updated on April 19, 2018.**
